Guide to the Bella Abzug papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Subject Files
  - Subseries V.23: Grants
    - Racism Awareness Center for Educators (Box 305)
    - Riverside Research Institute (Box 305)
    - Roosevelt Hospital (Box 305)
    - St. Albans Naval Hospital--Veterans (Box 305)
    - St. Clement's (Box 305)
    - St. Matthew's and St. Timothy's Center (Box 305)
    - Schuyler Arms (Box 305)
    - Seneca Nation of Indians (Box 305)
    - Summer Recreation Support Program (Box 305)
    - Toutz, Ron (opera) (Box 305)
    - Trade Zones (Box 305)
    - United Federation of Teachers (Box 305)
    - United Cancer Institute, Inc. (Box 305)
    - Upper Manhattan Youth Conservation Corps Program (Box 305)
    - Veterans (Box 305)
    - Village Voice (Box 305)
    - Visitation Monastery (Box 305)
    - W .H.A.M., Inc. (Box 305)
    - WNET New York (Box 305)
    - Wave Hill Mini-grant (Box 305)
    - Women Make Movies, Inc. (Box 306)
    - Women's Counseling Project. (Box 306)
    - Women's Interart Center (1 Folder, 4 volumes) (Box 306)
    - Women's Multi-Service Center (Box 306)
    - Yeshiva University (Box 306)
  - Subseries V.24: Handicapped
    - Correspondence (Box 307)
    - General (Box 307)
    - Blind Vendors (Box 307)
    - Children (Box 307)
    - Federation of the Handicapped (Box 308)
    - Deaf (Box 308)
    - In Touch (Box 308)
    - Joint Handicapped Council (Box 308)
    - Legislation:
      - General (Box 308)
      - Wagner-O'Day Act:
        - Correspondence (Box 308)
        - Abzug--Notes & Memos General (Box 308)
        - Bills & Amendments--drafts and copies (Box 308)
        - Hearings and Statements (Box 309)
        - Reports and Laws--copies (Box 309)
        - Printed--miscellaneous (Box 309)
    - New York City (Box 309)
    - President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped (Box 310)
    - Transportation, (2 Folders) (Box 310)
    - Transportation--Air (Box 310)
    - U.S. Department of H.E.W. (Box 310)
    - U. S. Department of Labor--Advisory Committee on Sheltered Workshops (Box 310)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation Printed (Box 310)
  - Subseries V.25: Health
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 311)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 312)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 313)
    - Abzug--Notes, memoranda, statements, activities, 1975 (Box 313)
    - General--1970-1976 (Box 314)
    - Aged:
      - General (Box 314)
      - New York City and State (Box 314)
    - Printed--Reports and Miscellaneous (Box 315)
    - Alcoholism—General (Box 315)
    - Alcoholics Anonymous (Box 315)
    - Freeport Hospital (Freeport, N.Y.) (Box 315)
    - New York City and State Printed (Box 315)
    - Ambulatory Services Cancer and Carcinogens (Box 316)
    - Coalition for Health Funding (Box 316)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning (SEE ALSO: Health--NYC--CHP) (Box 316)
    - Dental Care (Box 316)
    - Drug Abuse:
      - Correspondence (1) (Box 316)
      - Correspondence (2) (Box 317)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 317)
      - General (Box 317)
      - Congress, U.S.--Special Studies Subcommittee (Box 317)
      - Legislation (Box 317)
      - Marijuana (Box 317)
      - National Institute on Drug Abuse (Box 317)
      - New York City: (Box 318)
        - General, (2 Folders) (Box 318)
        - Addiction Services Agency, (2 Folders) (Box 318)
        - Programs: (Box 319)
          - General (Box 319)
          - Compass (Box 319)
          - Day Top Village (Box 319)
          - Horizon House (Box 319)
          - Odyssey House (Box 319)
          - Phoenix House (Box 319)
          - Reality House (Box 319)
          - Spark (Box 319)
      - New York State: (Box 320)
        - General, (2 Folders) (Box 320)
        - Narcotic Addiction Control Commission (Box 320)
        - Printed (Box 320)
    - Emergency Care (Box 321)
    - Family Planning:
      - Correspondence (Box 321)
      - Abzug--Notes and statements (Box 321)
      - General (Box 321)
      - Contraceptives (Box 321)
      - Intra-Uterine Devices (Box 321)
      - New York State (Box 321)
      - Sterilization (Box 321)
    - Printed--Reports and Periodicals (Box 322)
    - Fetal Research--Correspondence, General, Printed (Box 322)
    - Food and Drug Administration, U.S. (Box 322)
    - Health Maintenance Organizations-- (Box 323)
    - Health Manpower:
      - General, (2 Folders) (Box 323)
      - Nurses (Box 323)
      - Correspondence (Box 323)
      - General (Box 323)
      - Nurses--Training (Box 324)
      - Physicians' Assistants (Box 324)
    - Hearings and Testimony--Miscellaneous (Box 324)
    - Home Health Care (Box 324)
    - Hospitals:
      - Correspondence, (2 Folders) (Box 324)
      - General (Box 324)
      - New York City:
        - General Beekman (Box 324)
        - Bellevue (Box 324)
        - Beth Israel (Box 325)
        - Bird S. Coler (Box 325)
        - Delafield:
          - Correspondence (Box 325)
          - Abzug--statements, Notes, Memos. (Box 325)
          - General (Box 325)
        - French and Polyclinic (Box 326)
        - Goldwater (Box 326)
        - Gouverneur (Box 326)
        - Harlem (Box 326)
        - Jewish Memorial (Box 326)
        - Knickerbocker (Box 326)
        - Lincoln (Box 326)
        - Memorial Sloan-Kettering (Box 327)
        - Metropolitan (Box 327)
        - Morrisania (Box 327)
        - New York Hospital--Burn Center (Box 327)
        - Roosevelt (Box 327)
        - St. Clare's (Box 327)
        - St. Luke's (Box 327)
        - St. Vincent's (Box 327)
        - Sydenham (Box 327)
        - United Hospital Fund (Box 327)
        - Wadsworth (Box 327)
      - Public Health Service (Box 327)
    - Immunization (Box 328)
    - Insurance: (Box 328)
    - General (Box 328)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 328)
    - Federal Employees (Box 328)
    - Health Insurance Benefits Advisory Council (Box 329)
    - Unemployed (Box 329)
    - National Health Insurance:
      - Correspondence (Box 329)
      - Abzug--Notes and memoranda (Box 329)
      - Statements (Box 329)
      - General, (2 Folders) (Box 330)
      - Committee for National Health Insurance, (2 Folders) (Box 330)
      - Hearings and Testimony, 1971-1976 (Box 331)
      - Legislation, 92nd, 93rd (Box 331)
      - Legislation, 94th Congress (Box 332)
      - Nixon Administration Plan (Box 332)
      - Women (Box 332)
      - Printed--Reports (Box 332)
      - Printed—Miscellaneous (Box 333)
    - Lead Poisoning (Box 333)
    - Legislation:
      - Miscellaneous and n.d. (Box 333)
      - Abzug (Box 333)
      - 92nd Congress--General; HR 22 (Kennedy/GrHRths) (Box 333)
      - 93rd Congress: (Box 334)
        - House: General, (3 Folders) (Box 334)
        - HR 14721 (Health Manpower) (Box 334)
        - HR 16204 (National Health Planning) (Box 334)
      - 93rd Congress--Senate: General; S 2983 (Urban Hospitals) (Box 335)
      - 94th Congress--General; HR 21 (22,3209) (Health Security) (Box 335)
      - 94th Congress--HR 5546 (Health Manpower) (Box 336)
      - 94th Congress--HR 12678 (Health Information) (Box 336)
      - 94th Congress--HR 12937 (Maternal and Child Health) (Box 336)
      - 94th Congress--S 66 (Health Revenue Sharing) (Box 336)
    - Malpractice:
      - General; Abzug--Notes and memoranda; American Arbitration Association (Box 336)
      - Insurance: (Box 337)
        - Correspondence; General; Legislation (Box 337)
        - National Conference on Medical Malpractice, 1975 (Box 337)
        - Printed (Box 337)
    - Medicare/Medicaid: (Box 338)
      - Correspondence (Box 338)
      - Abzug--Statements and Notes (Box 338)
      - General (Box 338)
      - "Deeming" (Box 338)
      - Fraud and Medicaid "Mills" (Box 338)
      - New York City (Box 338)
      - New York State (Box 338)
      - Reports (Box 339)
      - Printed (Box 339)
    - Mental Health:
      - Correspondence and General (Box 339)
      - Community Mental Health Centers (Box 339)
      - Joint Council for Mental Health (Box 339)
      - Legislation (Box 339)
      - New York City:
        - General (Box 339)
        - The Bridge (Box 339)
        - Riverdale Mental Health Association, Inc (Box 339)
        - Washington Heights Mental Health Council (Box 340)
        - West Side Mental Health Catchment Area (Box 340)
        - Willowbrook (Box 340)
      - Psychosurgery:
        - General (Box 340)
        - Printed (Box 340)
    - Retardation (SEE ALSO: Child Care--Retarded Children) (Box 341)
    - Printed (Box 341)
    - National Health Council (Box 341)
    - New York City--General, (2 Folders) (Box 341)
    - New York City: (Box 342)
      - Coalition for Community Health (Box 342)
      - Comprehensive Health Planning Agency:
        - General (Box 342)
        - District profile, (8 volumes) (Box 342)
        - Manhattan North, (2 Folders) (Box 343)
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation--General (Box 343)
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation--Reports (Box 344)
      - Irvington House (Box 344)
      - Neighborhood Centers and Organizations:
        - General (Box 344)
        - Association of New York Neighborhood Health Centers (Box 344)
        - Chinatown Health Fair (Box 344)
        - Lower East Side Neighborhood Health Councils (Box 344)
        - Mid-Westside Neighborhood Health Council (Box 344)
        - Neighborhood Family Care Center (Lower Washington Ht) (Box 344)
        - Neighborhood Health Services Program (Box 344)
        - North East Neighborhood Association (Box 344)
        - Ryan Health Center (Box 344)
        - Upper Manhattan Community Health Association (Box 344)
    - New York State: (Box 345)
      - General (Box 345)
      - New York Metropolitan Regional Medical Program (Box 345)
      - Rochester (Box 345)
    - Occupational Safety and Health (Box 345)
    - Pharmacists and pharmaceuticals (Box 346)
    - Professional Standards Review Organizations (PBROs) (Box 346)
    - Public Health Service, U.S.: (Box 346)
    - Correspondence and General (Box 346)
    - Grants, Awards and Fellowships (Box 346)
    - Tay-Sachs disease (Box 347)
    - Tuberculosis (Box 347)
    - Venereal Disease (Box 347)
    - Vitamins and Minerals (Box 347)
    - Women:
      - General (Box 347)
      - Maternal and Child Health (Box 347)
    - Printed--Reports and Pamphlets, (2 Folders) (Box 347)
    - Printed: (Box 348)
      - Journals and Newsletters: (Box 348)
      - Health PAC Bulletin (Box 348)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 Folders) (Box 348)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 348)
  - Subseries V.26: Housing
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971, 1972-1974 (Box 349)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 350)
    - Abzug:
      - Memoranda (Box 350)
      - Notes (Box 350)
      - Speeches and statements, 1970-1973 and n.d. (Box 350)
      - Speeches and statements, 1974-1976 Miscellaneous activities (Box 351)
    - General (Box 351)
    - Aged (Box 351)
    - Community Development Block Grants (Box 351)
    - Co-operatives (Box 352)
    - Discrmination (Box 352)
    - Farmers Home Administration (U.S. Department of Agriculture) (Box 352)
    - Federal Housing Administration (Box 352)
    - Financing: (Box 352)
    - General (Box 352)
    - Federal National Mortgage Association (Box 352)
    - "Redlining" (Box 352)
    - Hearings and Testimony, 1971-1974 (Box 352)
    - Hearings and Testimony, 1975-1976 (Box 353)
    - Housing and Urban Development, U.S. Dept. of:
      - General, (2 Folders) (Box 353)
      - Programs--G.A.O. Report (Box 353)
      - Sects. 235-6 (Box 353)
    - Legislation: (Box 354)
      - By Abzug, 92nd--93rd Congresses; 93rd--94th Congresses (Box 354)
      - Miscellaneous and n.d. (Box 354)
      - Miscellaneous and n.d. (crime and security) (Box 354)
      - To 1970 (Box 354)
      - 92nd Congress:
        - General (Box 354)
        - Bills and laws (printed) (Box 354)
      - 93rd Congress: (Box 355)
        - General Bills and Reports (printed) (Box 355)
        - HR 14490 (Box 355)
        - HR 15361
          - General (Box 355)
          - Solar energy amendment (Box 355)
        - Better Communities Act (Box 356)
        - Homestead Acts (Box 356)
        - Housing & Community Development Act, (3 Folders) (Box 356)
        - Senate--General (Box 356)
        - Senate--S. 3066 (Box 357)
      - 94th Congress:
        - General (Box 357)
        - HR 5398 (Box 357)
    - Low and Moderate Income (Box 357)
    - Model Cities (Box 357)
    - Neighborhoods (Box 357)
    - New York City: (Box 358)
      - Correspondence (Box 358)
      - Abzug--Notes, memos, statements and activities (Box 358)
      - General, (3 Folders) (Box 358)
      - Buildings:
        - 6th st., 716 E. (Box 358)
        - 12th st., 302 W. 13th St., 128 W. (Box 358)
        - 17th st., 206-208 & 210-212 E. 19th st., 210 E. (Box 358)
        - 21st st., 360 W. Shelved (Box 359)
        - 24th st., 401 W. (Box 359)
        - 26th st., 229 W. (Box 359)
        - 38th st., 355 W. (Box 359)
        - 51st st., 427 W. (Box 359)
        - 63rd St., 258 W. (Box 359)
        - 101st st., 215 W. (Box 359)
        - l06th st., 206-210 W. (3rd World Tenants Union) (Box 359)
        - lllth st., 545 W. (Box 359)
        - ll2th st., W.--squatters (Box 359)
        - Amsterdam Ave., 830-832. Bennett Ave., 10 (Box 359)
        - Fairview, 45 (Inwood Co-op) (Box 359)
        - MacDougal St., 103-105 (Box 359)
        - Ansonia Hotel (Box 359)
        - Baruch Houses (Box 359)
        - Battery Park City (Box 359)
        - Birbach, Jerry--buildings (Box 359)
        - Bridge Towers (Box 359)
        - Bridge--Good Shepherd (Box 359)
        - Columbus Hospital Housing (Box 359)
        - Co-Op City (Box 359)
        - Dexter Hotel (Box 359)
        - Gouverneur Gardens (Box 359)
        - Hamilton Hotel (Box 359)
        - Inwood Terrace, Inc. (99 Hillside) (Box 359)
        - Inwood Towers (Box 359)
        - Jumel (Box 360)
        - LaGuardia Houses (Box 360)
        - Lavenberg (Box 360)
        - Lincoln Towers (Box 360)
        - Manhattan Plaza (Box 360)
        - Masaryk Tmo1ers (Box 360)
        - Meltzer Towers (Box 360)
        - Nevada Hotel (Box 360)
        - Parc Vendome (Box 360)
        - Pueblo Nuevo (Box 360)
        - Scott, Walter (Box 360)
        - Seward Park Co-Op (Box 360)
        - Skyview (Riverdale) (Box 360)
        - Southbridge Towers (Box 360)
        - Two Bridges (Box 360)
        - University Hotel (No-Ho) (Box 360)
        - University Settlement (Box 360)
        - Washbridge Apartments (Box 360)
        - Westbeth (Box 360)
        - Women's House of Detention (Box 360)
      - New York City: (Box 361)
        - Census Information (Box 361)
        - Chelsea (Box 361)
        - City Planning Commission (Box 361)
        - Clinton (Box 361)
        - Co-Operatives (Box 361)
        - Corporations (Private): (Box 361)
        - Alliance Holding Company (Podell Houses) (Box 361)
        - Investors Funding (Box 361)
        - Sackman-Gilliland (Box 361)
        - Emergency Repair Program (Box 361)
        - Housing and Development Administration:
          - General (Box 361)
          - Memoranda (Box 361)
          - Press Releases (Box 362)
          - Reports by and about Washington Hgts Neighborhood Preservation (Box 362)
      - Housing Authority (Box 362)
      - Institutional Expansion (Box 362)
      - Landmarks (Box 362)
      - Lawsuits (Box 362)
      - Legislation (Box 363)
      - Mitchell-Lama (Box 363)
      - Model Cities (Box 363)
      - Municipal Loan Program (Box 363)
      - Organizations--General (Box 363)
      - Organizations: (Box 364)
        - Community Preservation Corporation (Box 364)
        - Emergency Committee for the Rent Freeze (Box 364)
        - Esperanza (Box 364)
        - Housing Conservation Coordinators, (Gloria Milliken) (Box 364)
        - Metropolitan Council on Housing (Box 364)
        - Neighborhood Associations--misc. (Box 364)
        - Sherman Creek Organization for Renewal and Expansion (SCORE) (Box 364)
      - Projects and Programs--misc. (Box 364)
      - Relocation (Box 364)
      - Rent Control:
        - Correspondence (Box 364)
        - General (Box 364)
        - Laws, Regulations, Forms, Pamphlets (Box 365)
        - Lawsuits (Box 365)
        - Maximum Base Rent (Box 365)
        - Price Commission (Box 365)
      - Reports and Publications, Miscellaneous, (2 Folders) (Box 366)
      - Squatters (Box 366)
      - New York City: (Box 367)
        - Tenants Organizations and Programs:
          - General (Box 367)
          - Center for Tenants Rights (Box 367)
        - Urban Home Ownership Corporation (Box 367)
        - Welfare Hotels and Single Room Occupancy:
          - General (Box 367)
          - Reports and Studies (Box 367)
        - Zoning (Box 367)
        - Printed--clippings (Box 367)
    - New York State: (Box 368)
      - General (Box 368)
      - Housing Finance (Box 368)
      - Legislation (Box 369)
      - Lists (Box 369)
      - Mitchell-Lama (Box 369)
      - N.Y.S. Association of Renewal and Housing Officials, Inc. (NYSARHO) (Box 369)
    - Nixon, Richard M.--Administration Policies (see also: Housing--Legislation--93rd Congress--Better Communities Act) (Box 370)
    - Rehabilitation (Box 370)
    - Rent and Rent Control (Box 370)
    - Safety and Crime (Box 370)
    - Subsidies, (2 Folders) (Box 370)
    - Taxes (Box 371)
    - Urban Renewal (Box 371)
    - Printed: (Box 371)
    - Reports, Periodicals, Pamphlets, (2 Folders) (Box 371)
    - Congressional Record (Box 371)
    - Federal Register, (2 Folders) (Box 372)
    - Clippings (Box 372)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 372)
  - Subseries V.27: Immigration
    - Correspondence (Box 373)
    - General (Box 373)
    - Illegal Aliens (Box 373)
    - Justice, U.S. Department of--Immigration and Naturalization Service--Publications (Box 373)
    - Legislation (Box 373)
  - Subseries V.28: Indochina
    - Correspondence--[n.d.], 1970-1971, (4 Folders) (Box 374)
    - Correspondence, 1972, (4 Folders) (Box 375)
    - Correspondence, 1972, (4 Folders) (Box 376)
    - Correspondence, 1972, (4 Folders) (Box 377)
    - Correspondence, 1973, (4 Folders) (Box 378)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 379)
    - Correspondence, 1975, (4 Folders) (Box 380)
    - Correspondence, 1975, (4 Folders) (Box 381)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 381)
    - Abzug: (Box 382)
      - "Barnstorming" Tours SEE: Peace Movement (Box 382)
      - Congressional Record Statements (typescripts) (Box 382)
      - Congressional Record Statements (printed) (Box 382)
      - Mailing List (Box 382)
      - Memoranda and notes (Box 382)
      - Press Releases (Box 382)
      - Speeches and statements (Box 382)
      - Testimony (Box 382)
      - Trips: (Box 383)
        - Paris, 1972 (Box 383)
        - Southeast Asia, 1973
          - General (Box 383)
          - Background Material (Box 383)
          - Narcotics Information (Box 383)
          - Printed (Box 383)
        - Southeast Asia, 1975 (Box 384)
          - Correspondence (Box 384)
          - Background Material, (2 Folders) (Box 384)
          - Briefing Book (Box 385)
          - Briefing Materials, miscellaneous (Box 385)
          - Cambodia (Box 385)
          - Embassy (U. S.) Kit (Box 385)
          - Press (Box 385)
          - Schedules, Notes, Memos, Memorabilia (Box 385)
          - See Also--Photographs, Box (Box 385)
    - General, [n.d.], 1970-1976 (Box 386)
    - Cambodia:
      - Correspondence (Box 386)
      - Abzug--Notes, memoranda and statements (Box 386)
      - General (Box 386)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 386)
      - Lawsuit (Box 387)
      - Mayaguez Incident (Box 387)
      - Printed Material (Box 387)
    - Congress, U.S.--Anti-War Activities (Box 387)
    - Democratic Party (U.S.) (Box 387)
    - Elections, Vietnam (Box 387)
    - Hearings and Testimony (Box 387)
    - Indochina Resource Center (See Also: Printed--Reports) (Box 388)
    - Lavelle, General John D. (Box 388)
    - Legislation:
      - General (Box 388)
      - Sponsored by Abzug (Box 388)
      - 92nd Congress:
        - General (Box 388)
        - Defense Appropriations (Box 388)
        - People's Peace Treaty Concurrent Resolution (Box 388)
        - Resolution of Inquiry (Box 388)
        - Resolution of Inquiry--Pentagon Papers (Box 388)
    - Legislation: (Box 389)
      - 93rd Congress:
        - General (Box 389)
        - Foreign Aid (Box 389)
      - 94th Congress:
        - General (Box 389)
        - HR 6096 (Vietnam Evacuation) (Box 389)
        - HRes 129 (Resolution of Inquiry) (Box 389)
    - Medical Aid (Box 389)
    - Oil (Box 389)
    - Organizations: (Box 390)
      - General (Box 390)
      - American Friends Service Committee (Box 390)
      - Coalition to Stop Funding the War (Box 390)
      - Committee of Responsibility (Box 390)
      - Indochina Peace Campaign (Box 390)
      - Vietnam Veterans Against the War (Box 390)
      - War Resisters' League (Box 390)
      - Women's Strike for Peace (Box 390)
      - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 390)
    - Paris Peace Talks (Box 390)
    - Pentagon Papers (Box 390)
    - Political Prisoners: (Box 391)
      - Correspondence (Box 391)
      - Abzug--Statements, notes and memoranda (Box 391)
      - General (Box 391)
      - Organizations (Box 391)
      - Reports (Box 391)
      - Thanh, Ngo Ba (Box 391)
    - Prisoners of War: (Box 391)
    - Correspondence (Box 391)
    - General (See also: OVERSIZE) (Box 391)
    - Hearings (Box 391)
    - Protest Literature and Anti-War Activities: (Box 391A)
      - United States (See also: PEACE MOVEMENT) (Box 391A)
      - Europe (Box 391A)
      - Vietnam (Nguyen Xuan Nham A Corner of Hell) (Box 391A)
    - Refugees and Orphans: (Box 392)
      - General (Box 392)
      - Legislation (Box 392)
      - Orphans (Box 392)
      - Reports--Inter-Agency Task Force on Indo-China Refugees (Box 392)
      - Reports--General (Box 392)
    - Statistics and Data (Box 393)
    - Vietnamese Government Statements (Box 393)
    - Vietnamese Legislators and Citizens--Statements (Box 393)
    - War Crimes:
      - General (Box 393)
      - My Lai; Lt. William L. Calley (Box 393)
      - Winter Soldier Investigation (Box 393)
      - Printed Material (Box 393)
    - Photographs (Box 394)
    - Printed--Reports--General, (3 Folders) (Box 394)
    - Printed--Reports--Vietnamese (6 volumes.) (Box 395)
    - Printed: (Box 396)
      - Congressional Record (Box 396)
      - Periodicals (Box 396)
      - Reports, U.S. Congress (Box 396)
      - Miscellaneous (See also: OVERSIZE) (Box 396)
    - Printed--Clippings, (4 Folders) (Box 397)
  - Subseries V.29: Jewry
    - Correspondence--1970-1976 (Box 398)
    - Abzug--Statements, Activities, Notes and Memoranda (Box 398)
    - General (Box 398)
    - Congregations and Schools (Box 399)
    - Organizations:
      - Correspondence (Box 399)
      - General (Box 399)
      - American Jewish Committee (Box 399)
      - B'nai B'rith (Box 399)
      - Hadassah (Box 399)
      - Jewish Community Council of Washington Heights and Inwood (Box 399)
      - Zionist Organization of America (Box 399)
    - Poland (Warsaw) (Box 399)
    - Poverty (Box 399)
    - Soviet Jewry: (Box 400)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 400)
      - Abzug--Statements, Activities, Notes, Memoranda (Box 400)
      - General (Box 400)
      - Organizations: (Box 401)
        - General (Box 401)
        - American Jewish Conference on Soviet Jewry (Box 401)
        - National Council on Soviet Jewry (Box 401)
      - Rigerman Case (Box 401)
      - Solidarity Sunday (Box 401)
      - Printed Material (Box 401)
    - Syrian Jews (Box 401)
    - Women (Box 401)
    - Printed (Box 401)
  - Subseries V.30: Labor and Employment
    - Correspondence--1970-1974 (Box 402)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 403)